{
    "id": "7a1b89bf7cd34231ad2c81bcd8bcb95e",
    "title": "Identify The Adverb",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Surely you are not going out in that torn coat?",
            "description": "Most words ending in â€“ly are adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "surely",
                "going",
                "that",
                "torn"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "05f970fcc7bd4b7e8607382d804796e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can always come and stay with us if you want to.",
            "description": "Words that say how often something happens are adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "always",
                "with",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1f3aba7a52a14463b1186fdae09ce96b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ever played rugby?",
            "description": "Words that say how often something happens are adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "ever",
                "played",
                "rugby"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6c643353af8041b68368d05677b3a52f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your bicycle just needs some oil.",
            "description": "Just is an example of a focusing adverb because it points to one part of a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "needs",
                "some",
                "oil"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d1916b6897574ed8b5bc2f980c7ae675"
        },
        {
            "question": "The flight has obviously been delayed.",
            "description": "Most words ending in -ly are adverbs. Obviously is one of them.",
            "answers": [
                "flight",
                "has",
                "obviously",
                "been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3be92676c60f42b0b4694e0211d5f510"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is my mother, but she is also my best friend.",
            "description": "Words like also, as well and too are adverbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "but",
                "also",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4522934a48444b10a54c13a1bb700e2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has a new hairstyle every week.",
            "description": "Most words indicating time and frequency are adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "new",
                "week",
                "every week"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "990da4f2f42241a09ee732632c5d11b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The invitees have already turned up.",
            "description": "Words like already, soon, last, just and still are all adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "invitees",
                "already",
                "turned"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "340120cc7dc140629bbcab1a50a85f06"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have definitely been working too hard.",
            "description": "Here too modifies the adjective hard. A word modifying an adjective is an adverb. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "been",
                "working",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "cfb7151e8e634a70bef80acf1b9060ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "She speaks English remarkably well.",
            "description": "Here the words well and remarkably are both adverbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "speaks",
                "remarkably",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "55b7fae0ceb94ea5ac9d86d895b6f8f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We did not achieve much improvement in sales last year.",
            "description": "Time words are all adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "much",
                "in",
                "last year"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "6828e0ffe39f4264aacf638aa5c2ab03"
        },
        {
            "question": "This time tomorrow I will be happily working in my garage.",
            "description": "Time words are adverbs. Most words ending in -ly are also adverbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "tomorrow",
                "happily",
                "my",
                "garage"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "01290c4f92ec41c8951bfa615b60c832"
        }
    ]
}